(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-03T13:31:07.255280",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
それじゃあそれでいいのね
from then on, if that's fine with you...
だからね、どうなの？ねえ
then, you know, how about that?
ねえ
Hey.
いやだ
I don't want to.
なんで？
Why?
いいの、このままでさあ
It's fine as it is, right?
ねえ
Hey.
すごっ！偉い！
Amazing! Great!
あれはさ、おにぎり
That is, you know, a rice ball.
それが一番いいのでは？
That's the best one, right?
な訳
No way.
絶対成るほだり
It's bound to be great, right?
ねえ
Hey.
本当？本当？
Is it really? Is it really?
早く、急げっ！
Hurry, hurry!
ほいっ、ほいっ、ほいっ
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
おおっ！
Oh!
ほいっ、ほいっ、ほいっ
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
そうそう
There you go.
出る？
Really?
うそじゃないよ、出ておいで
It's not like that, come on over.
とっても居心地良くだね
It's very comfortable, you know.
みんなのコメント見るのが大好きなんだから僕
I love looking at everyone's comments, so I...
行くぞっ！
Here we go!
にゃあ、パチパチパチっ！
Yeah, nice, nice!
あると思う
I think there is.
うーん、みんな好きだけどね
Hmm, I love everyone, but you know...
わっ、それはやばい！
Wait, that's bad!
やばいっ、これね、これね
Wait, wait! This is...
しょうがないよね
Well, it can't be helped, right?
にゃ、にゃんよー！にゃ、にゃ、にゃ！
Nya, nya, yo! Nya, nya, nya!
やったー！ほっ、ほいっ！にゃっ！
Yay! Hooray! Nya!
おっ！うあっ！やあっ！
Oh! Yeah!
すー、にゃっ！にゃあっ！
Yay! Nya! Yay! Nya!
僕のせいじゃないよ！ほいっ、しーらねっ、にゃっ！
It's not my fault, yo! Hoi! Shh! Nya!
店長っ！にゃ、どんまい、どんまいっ！
Director! Nya, don't mind, don't mind!
にゃ、にゃーん！なんで？ねこまざい？
Nya, nya! Why? Nya, nyan-zain?
すごい、すごい！お邪魔しまーす、うわっ！
Amazing, amazing! Interfere, wa!
あ、ぬるまゆー！
Ah, it's lukewarm!
おかゆーっ！
Okayu!
ぱん！にゃ！ぱん！へへへへへっ！
Pan! Nya! Pan! Hehehehehe!
にゃ？ぷーっ、ふふっ！ぷーっ！
Nya? Phew! Hahaha! Phew!
ねーっ！ぎゅっ！へへっ！ほいっ！
Ne-i-gyu! Hehe! Hoi!
えにふっ！ふふっ！
Enif! Hehe!
おーい！ねえっ！はーいっ！
Oi! Nee! Hi!
十っ！
Ten!
九っ！
Nine!
八っ！
Eight!
七っ！
Seven!
六っ！
Six!
五っ！
Five!
四、三、二、一っ！
Four! Three! Two! One!
ここはとある田舎のおにぎり屋さん
This is a certain rural onigiri shop.
そこにはゲームが大好きなばあちゃんと…
There lived a grandma who loved games...
猫が住んでいました。
and a cat.
すっかり影響を受けてゲーマーのようです。
It seems she was heavily influenced and became a gamer.
ある日この村にクマの着ぐるみがチラシを配りに来ていました。
One day, a bear in a suit came to the village distributing flyers.
内容は、アイドルオーディション開催中！という内容でした。
The content was that an idol audition was being held.
この猫はゲームばっかりしてたので、
This cat had only been playing games,
自分にはちょっと難しいかも…と思いました。
so she thought it might be a bit too difficult for her.
あっ…
Ah...
これだったら…ちょっとやってみたいかも…
If it's this, maybe she'd want to try it out a bit...
でもお店のこともあるしな…
But she also had the shop to think about, so...
とりあえずオーディション受けてみたら？
"Why don't you try auditioning, for now?"
誰でもできることじゃないんだし…
"It's not something just anyone can do, after all..."
なにより、やってみたいんでしょう？
"More than anything, don't you want to try it?"
そんな顔してるわよ。"
"I can tell by the look on your face."
「あんた、昔からゲームも好きだったけど
"You've always loved games, of course,"
人を笑顔にすることが大好きだったじゃない"
"but you always loved making people smile, didn't you?"
アイドルか…
An idol...
僕がホロライブに入ったらどんな風になってるんだろう？
What would it be like if I joined Hololive?
今はまだ想像できないや…
I still can't picture it yet...
生の本音はエグいから
Raw honest feelings are too harsh,
ちゃんと火を通して食べてね (もぐもぐ)
so cook them thoroughly before eating! (Munch, munch)
リップサービスはズルいかな？
is lip service a bit sly?
それも以心伝心のレシピ
Or is that also a recipe for telepathy?
みんなー、自分偽ってるかい？ (いえす！)
Everyone, are you deceiving yourselves? (Yes!)
嘘の万国博覧会
A universal exposition of lies!
みんなー、自分偽ってるかい？ (いえす！)
Everyone, are you deceiving yourselves? (Yes!)
痛みを飼いならして (シャー)
Taming the pain... (Hiss!)
嫌いだけど「スキ」、不味くても「オイシイ」
Although I hate it, I say "I like it", even if it tastes bad I say "It's delicious".
着ぐるみを着てハグしてあげる (らびゆー)
I'll wear a costume and give you a hug! (Loving you)
泣かせないように 怒らせないように
So as not to make you cry, so as not to make you angry,
ちょうど良く君と遊びたいのだ
I just want to play with you nicely!
ネコカブリーナ (にゃー) 猫かぶりな (にゃー)
Neko Kaburina (Meow), Pretending to be a cat (Meow),
ちょっと臆病な君が好き
I like you, who are a bit timid.
ネコカブリーナ (にゃー) 猫かぶりな (にゃー)
Neko Kaburina (Meow), Pretending to be a cat (Meow),
取り繕ってるぼくが好き？
Do you like me, who am putting up a front?
弱さを知ってる君が好きだよ
I like you, who know what weakness is!
「思う」と「言う」では大違い
There is a big difference between "thinking" and "saying".
建て前も用法と用量次第
Pretense depends on dosage and directions.
みんな～ 自分偽ってるかい？
Are you all pretending to be someone else?
ひとりぼっちの音楽隊
A lonely marching band.
みんな～ 自分偽ってるかい？
Are you all pretending to be someone else?
首輪の鈴鳴らして
Ringing the bell on our collars.
災難だけど「ハッピー」
It's a disaster, but "Happy"!
しんどくても「ヘイキ」
Even when it's tough, "I'm fine"!
アベコベな夢を見せてあげる
I'll show you an upside-down dream.
傷つけないように 追い詰めないように
So as not to hurt or corner you,
夜明けまで君とふざけあうのだ
We'll fool around together until dawn.
ネコカプリーナ 猫かぶりな
Neko-kaprina, wearing a cat disguise.
爪を丸めてる君が好き
I like you with your claws rounded in.
ネコカプリーナ 猫かぶりな
Neko-kaprina, wearing a cat disguise.
涙を見せないぼくが好き？
Do you like me who never shows tears?
痛みを知ってる君が好きだよ
I love you, who knows what pain feels like.
君は猫 猫 ファスナーつきの猫
You're a cat, a cat with a zipper.
君は人 人 ファスナーつきの人
You're a person, a person with a zipper.
あれはUFO UFO ファスナーつきのUFO
That's a UFO, a UFO with a zipper.
君は猫 猫 ファスナーつきの猫
You're a cat, a cat with a zipper.
君は人 人 ファスナーつきの人
You're a person, a person with a zipper.
あれはUFO UFO ファスナーつきのUFO
That's a UFO, a UFO with a zipper.
君は誰？ 誰？ 特別な人
Who are you? Who? A special person.
ネコカプリーナ 猫かぶりな
Neko-kaprina, wearing a cat disguise.
ちょっと臆病な君が好き
I like you who are a bit timid.
君もぼくも馴染めない世界でやっと見つけた居場所だから
Because this is the place we finally found
ネコカプリーナ 猫かぶりな
Neko-kaprina, wearing a cat disguise.
取り繕ってるぼくが好き？
Do you like me who am putting up a front?
君もぼくもどうかっしてる世界で
In a world where both you and I are going crazy,
明日もまた会えたら良いな
I hope we can meet again tomorrow.
ネコカプリーナ ネコカプリーナ
Neko-kaprina, Neko-kaprina...
弱さを知ってる君が好きだよ
I love you, who knows what weakness feels like.
もしもし～！ころさん？
Hello~! Korone-san?
ごめんね仕事終わりにさ
Sorry for calling right after work...
おかゆ～！ううん全然大丈夫だよ！
Okayu~! No, it's totally fine!
嬉しいな おかゆからの電話…
I'm so happy to get a call from Okayu...
えへへ…ころさん ホロライブって知ってる？
Hehe... Korone-san, do you know about Hololive?
名前くらいは知ってるけど…どうしたの？
I know the name, but... why do you ask?
んーー…僕と一緒にデビューしてみない？
Hmm... Would you like to debut together with me?
えっ！？なになにどういうことどういうこと！？ でもおかゆとだったらいいかも…うん！
Eh!? What do you mean!? But if it's with Okayu, it might be nice... Yeah!
ほんと！よーーし！
Really? Alriiiiight!
そうと決まれば！善は急げだあああ！
If that's decided! There's no time to lose!
ねぇ まだまだまだ？急いで！
Hey, are you still not ready? Hurry up!
出かける準備はできたかい？
Are you ready to head out?
キミに見せたい不思議の世界 見送りならいらない
I want to show you a mysterious world. No need to see me off.
たとえ火の中水の中 手さぐりで見えない今日の中
Even through fire and water, fumbling in today where we can't see anything,
1秒先だってまだ知らないけど
Even though we don't know what a second from now holds,
いつも思い出はどれも 全部ボールの中に
Every single memory is safely inside the Poké Ball.
1・2・3で飛び込め
Dive in on 1, 2, 3!
いつか描いた未来が ボクのポケットにあるから
Because the future we once imagined is right in my pocket.
はじめましてはいつだって初めてさ ためらうことなどない
First times are always a first time, nothing to hesitate about.
トライ！ Let's have a fight!
Try! Let's have a fight!
1.バトルをしたなら
1. If we battle,
2.笑うか泣いたって
2. Whether we laugh or cry,
3.で仲間になろうよ
3. Let's become friends!
あの日だってこの日だっていつだってそうしていた
We've always done that on days like then and days like today.
先も見えない果ても知らない世界がそこにあるけど
Even though a world where we can't see ahead or know the limits is right there,
レッツゴー 転んですりむいて
Let's go, tripping and scraping our knees,
レッツゴー 何度も歩き出す隣
Let's go, stepping forward side by side time and again.
キミにきめた！
I choose you!
隣の街から景色はため息つくほど 世界はめまぐるしく変わり 変わる ボクを置き去りにする
From the neighboring town, the scenery makes us sigh, the world changes so dizzyingly, leaving me behind.
子供の頃には夢中でくぐり抜けた穴ぼこでも しばらくぶりだな見落としていたの? でもね忘れた景色も今日のどこかにあるよ
Even that pothole we eagerly squeezed through in childhood—it's been a while, did I overlook it? But those forgotten scenes are somewhere in today.
1・2・3で飛び出せ
Dash out on 1, 2, 3...
今日の どこかにあるよ
Today's somewhere out there...
1・2・3で飛び出せ
Jump out with 1, 2, 3!
散々だって泣いていた
Crying that it was a mess,
日々 と ボール の 外 まで
days and beyond the ball's reach,
「どこへ行こうか」は
"Where shall we go?"
「どこへだって行けるでしょ?」
"We can go anywhere, right?"
息つく 暇など ない トライ! トライ!
There's no time to even breathe! Try, try!
Why don't we go?
1 言葉を超えて 2
Transcending words, 1,
境界線の先の まだ見ぬ君まで
to still-unseen you beyond the boundary line, 2,
倒れるなら 手をつくなら 前だって決めたんだ
If I fall, if I reach out, I decided to go forward!
日が沈むように影伸びて 背丈も変わっているけど
Shadows lengthen like the setting sun, our heights have changed too, but
レッツゴー!
Let's go!
雨上がりでなくちゃ
It has to be after the rain,
レッツゴー!
Let's go!
晴れ間に虹はない
without clearing, there is no rainbow.
あの日から気づいている
I've noticed since that day.
君は 君は
You, you,
いつの間にかやらか大人になっちゃいないかい?
have you somehow grown up before we knew it?
ほこりを被った ボロ着の 右ポケットに置いてきた
Left behind in the right pocket of dusty, tattered clothes,
片手に収まる冒険 ボクらの全てだった
adventure fitting in one hand was everything to us.
あの頃の思い出が 君を探しているよ
Memories of those days are searching for you!
1・2・3で飛び込め
Dive in with 1, 2, 3!
いつか描いた未来がボクの ポケットにあるから
The future we once envisioned is in my pocket, so
どこへ行こうよ
let's go somewhere!
どこへだって連れてってよ
Take me anywhere!
ためらうことなど ない トライ! トライ!
There's no hesitation, try, try!
Let's have a fight!
1 バトルをしたら 2
If we battle, 1, 2,
笑うか泣いたって3で 仲間になろうよ
whether we laugh or cry, let's become friends at 3!
あの日だって この日だって いつだってそうしていた
That day, this day, it was always like that.
先も見えない 果ても知らない 世界がそこにあるけど
A world where we don't know the end or beyond is right there, but
レッツゴー!
Let's go!
転んですりむいて
Stumbling and scraping our knees,
レッツゴー!
Let's go!
何度も歩き出す隣 キミにきめた!
I chose you by my side as I walk again and again!
Oh… しんでしまうとは 情けない
Oh... To die like this...
情けない!
is pathetic!
3.2.1… 王!
3, 2, 1... King!
王!
King!
なに? HELP!
What? HELP!
何事じゃ ひい
What's wrong? Eek!
姫がさらわれましたぁ
The princess has been kidnapped!
勇者は?
The hero?
いません
Isn't here.
うーん、そうだ!
Hmm, I know!
かくなる上はお前が勇者だ
In that case, you are the hero!
設定崩壊••!!
Setting broken!!
さぁ、その宝箱の中身とこのなけなしの金で旅立って仲間を探して化けもん倒して••
Now go set off with that treasure chest's contents and meager gold, find companions, and defeat the monsters...
••適当だねぇか
Well, that's pretty casual!
とにかく困ったら町のの人々に話しかけようぜ ボスとか全然倒せる!倒せる! マ・ジ・デ!
Anyway, if you're in trouble, talk to the townspeople! You can totally beat the bosses! Beat them! Seriously!
ばって ばって ばって 当然
Brag, brag, brag, naturally,
だって実際に一番偉いから!
because actually, I'm the greatest!
人ごみたくいってくれるぜ
You speak to us like we're lesser beings,
まったくもって上から目線すぎるぜ..
totally looking down on us from above!
経験値 経験値 経験値 積んで
Gain experience, gain experience, gain experience, pile it up,
もっと屈強な仲間探したまえ!
and find even tougher companions!
ていうか私は一兵卒です
I mean, I'm just a foot soldier!
有給休暇がデリート!デリート!
Paid leave is a date! A date!
「そなたがラスボスを倒してくる日を楽しみに待っておるぞい!」
"I'm looking forward to the day you defeat the final boss!"
世界平和を取り戻すため お国の平和を守るため
To reclaim world peace, to protect our country's peace,
一番
first...
Oh…しんでしまうとはなさけない！
Oh... If you die, that won't do!
3.2.1…×××!!
3, 2, 1... ×××!!
「王!」
"King!"
「なに?」
"What?"
「HELP!」
"HELP!"
「何事じゃ」
"What's wrong?"
「ひっ、姫がさらわれましたぁ!」
"H-The princess has been kidnapped!"
「勇者は?」
"The hero?"
「いません」
"Absent."
「うーん、そうだ!かくなる上はお前が勇者だ」
"Well, that settles it! You are the hero now!"
設定崩壊••!!
Setting broken...!!
「さあ、その宝箱の中身とこのなかなしの金で旅立って仲間を探して化け物倒して••」
"Now go, use the contents of that treasure chest and that meager gold to set off, find companions, and defeat the monsters..."
(••適当じゃねえか)
(That's pretty random!)
「とにかく困ったら町のひとたちに話しかけようぜ?ボスとか全然倒せる!倒せる!マ・ジ・デ!」
"Anyway, if you're in trouble, talk to the townspeople! You can totally beat the boss! Beat him! MA-JI-DE!"
いばって いばって いばって 当然
Right, right, right, obviously!
だって実際に一番偉いからでからです
Because we're actually the most important ones, after all!
人ごとみたいに扱ってくれるぜ
Treating people like subordinates,
まったくもって上から目線すぎぜ..
you're way too condescending...
経験値 経験値 経験値 積んで
Accumulating EXP, EXP, EXP,
もっと屈強な仲間探したまえ!
we gotta find stronger companions!
てゆおか私は一兵卒です
Teyuhika, I'm just a foot soldier.
有給休暇がデリート!デリート!
Paid leave is a date! A date!
「あなたがラスボスを倒してくる日を楽しみにしておるぞい!」
"Looking forward to the day you defeat the final boss!"
世界平和を取り戻す為、
To restore world peace,
お国の平和を守る為、
to protect our country's peace,
一番後ろでシキを取ります
we'll take the rear and take notes.
あなたの経験値を伝えましょう
Let's pass on your experience points!
あなたの為に 世界の為に
For you, for the world,
戦う僕らの愛国心
our patriotic hearts are fighting!
仲間も死んで絶滅寸前
Even our comrades died and we're on the verge of extinction—
やっぱりレベルが足りねえ..orz
guess our level wasn't high enough... orz
「あなたのパーティーは全滅しました。おお、神様よ! アーメン」
"Your party has been completely wiped out. Oh, Lord! Amen."
おお!しんでしまうとはなさけない!
Oh! If you die, that's pathetic!
させればそなたにもういちど、きかいをあたえよう
If you do, I'll give you another chance!
「王様っ」
"King?"
「なんですか」
"What is it?"
「もう…!」
"HELP!"
もう無理です
"It's impossible."
「えぇーっ!弱音を吐くとはもっと情けなぁぁぁい!」
"What?! Expressing weakness is even more pathetic!"
経済力、軍事力ともに申し分ない我が国は当然、
Our country is naturally top-tier in both economic and military power,
優秀な人材も潤沢、人望暑いね
and we're overflowing with brilliant talent!
ただ、ひとつ万国的な問題点は国家元首の本音さ
Only one universal problem: the head of state's true nature.
よく言えば無垢、悪く言えば.. O・BA・KA
Put nicely, it's flawless; put bluntly... O・BA・KA!
正真正銘 全人類は戦闘民族 言うまでもない (OK?)
To state the obvious, all humans are a warrior race, needless to say (OK?).
協調性や、順応性が重要なんて
Saying cooperation and adaptability are important?
ウキヨはクソゲーか?!
What is this, a crappy game?!
次のレベルになるには あと1000ポイントの経験が
To reach the next level, you need 1,000 more EXP.
さらにはもっと自己主張が必要じゃ くじけるな OK?
What's more, you need more self-assertion, so don't get discouraged, OK?
テリッサ ボロソン ザンシ パロントわ
Terissa, doroson, zanshi, paronto—
魔法使いも使いもんになってきたが
even the mages are becoming useless.
余裕しゃくしゃくうさら笑いで ごたくばっかり並べてしゃくにさわるぜ..
Grinning with a smug face, stacking up excuses, rubbing it in our faces!
ホリット ホリット ホリット ばっか
Holitt, holitt, holitt, bakka—
僧侶はホリットばっかでバカなの?
are the clerics just full of holitts and idiots?
王のアタシを眠らすなんてあんたいったい何様?さては謀反か?
Interrupting the king's nap, just who do you think you are? Is this treason?
「僕は勇者ではありません。むしろ王が勇者だと思いまーす!」
"I am not the hero! I think the king is the hero instead!"
世界平和を取り戻す為、
To restore world peace,
お国の平和を守る為、
to protect our country's peace,
最前線に身を投じませ
we throw ourselves onto the front lines,
支持率アップは目に見えた! (おいこら)
and our approval rating surge is plain to see! (Hey, come on!)
権益のため お金ののため
Fighting for authority, fighting for money—
戦う王様 何を見る
what is the fighting king even looking at?
近衛も瀕死絶滅寸前
Even the royal guard is on the verge of starvation and extinction—
しんでしまうとはなさけなぁぁぁい!
if you die, how pathetic!
世界平和を取り戻す為、
To restore world peace,
あなたの笑顔を守る為、
to protect your smile,
魔王軍関連情報を 命からがらにかき集め
we desperately scrape together intel on the Demon King's army,
今日も今日とて鎮座している まことの勇者を待っている
and today too, we sit on our thrones, waiting for a true hero!
他力本願ではありません
It's not about leaving things to others,
お城じゃ奴らにかなわねぇ::
we just can't beat the castle guards::
my little sister, i love you
my little angel, very very cute
do you know what i mean?
聞いて 聞いて 私 お姉ちゃんなだよ
Listen, listen, I'm the big sister!
遊ぼ 遊ぼ あなた まだ 喋れないよね?
Play with me, play with me! You still can't talk yet, right?
お下がり普通は嫌でしょ?
Acting all high and mighty usually sucks, right?
むしろ柔らかんできてっる
Rather, I've been coming prepared.
完璧を演じなくっちゃ
I've gotta act all perfect,
理想のお姉ちゃんなもん
'cause I'm the ideal big sister!
弱さを見せないことが逆に弱点なんです
Not showing any weakness—that's actually a weak point in itself.
平等にチャンスはあるから負けない私!
Everyone gets an equal chance, so I won't lose!
あなたの夢は右で
Your dream is on the right,
私の夢は左
and my dream is on the left.
ゆらゆらと迷っても
Even if we wander around swaying,
諦めない性格よ
we have a stubborn personality!
泣きたい時は泣いて
When you want to cry, cry it out;
笑いたい時は笑って
when you want to laugh, laugh it out!
疲れたら休みましょう
When you're tired, let's take a rest;
困ったら相談乗るから
when you're troubled, I'll hear you out.
理由があるとするれば
If there's a reason for it all,
あなたは私の天使
you are my angel.
my little sister, I love you
my little angel, very very cute
Do you know what I mean?
聞いて聞いて 私お姉ちゃんなんだよ
Listen, listen, I'm your older sister, you know?
遊ぼ遊ぼ あなたまだ喋れないのね?
Let's play, let's play, you still can't talk yet, can you?
お下がり 普通は嫌でしょ?
Hand-me-downs are usually unappealing, right?
むしろ喜んで着てる
Rather, I'm happily wearing them
完璧を演じなくちゃ
I've got to act like a perfectionist
理想のお姉ちゃんだもん
Since I'm the ideal older sister, you see
弱さを見せないこと逆が弱点なんです
Not showing weakness is actually a weakness itself
平等にチャンスはあるから… 負けるな私!
Since there's a fair chance available... don't lose, me!
あなたの夢は右で 私の夢は左
Your dream is on the right, and my dream is on the left
ゆらゆらと迷っても 諦めない性格よ
Even if I waver unsteadily, I have a personality that never gives up
泣きたい時は泣いて 笑いたい時は笑って
When you want to cry, cry, when you want to laugh, laugh
疲れたら休みましょう 困ったら相談乗るから
When you get tired, let's take a rest, if you're troubled, I'll listen
理由があるとするれば あなたは私の天使
If there's a reason, it's because you are my angel
my little sister, I love you
my little angel, very very cute
Do you know what I mean?
そっぽ向かれて話しすらできない
Being turned away from so I can't even talk
心配しすぎ? 話せないことだってある
Am I worrying too much? There are things we can't talk about either
私は私でヤバい 手抜きは絶対NG
I'm struggling in my own way, too, slacking off is strictly NG
完璧を演じなくちゃ 理想のお姉ちゃんだもん
I've got to act like a perfectionist since I'm the ideal older sister, you see
レベル上げとく ィノ(得いな)方で努力は惜しまない
I'm good at leveling up and don't spare any effort
神様は必ず見てるよ… 頑張っちゃう!
God is definitely watching... I'll do my best!
作った笑顔じゃない あなたのホントが好き
Not a fabricated smile, I love the real you
イライラが溜まったら 甘いもの食べちゃおう
If frustration builds up, let's eat some sweets
認め たくない時ほど認めて
Accept things even more when you don't want to admit them
悔しい時は眠って
When you feel frustrated, sleep
雨の日は羽休み 濡れてたら拭いてあげるから
On rainy days, rest your wings, if you're getting wet, I'll wipe you dry
理由があるとするれば そんな表情するんだね
If there's a reason... you made that kind of expression, huh?
初めて見た可愛いいよ
It's the first time I saw it, it's cute
自慢だから自信持って 見ておいでよ世界を
Be proud of it, have some confidence, come and look at the world
あの子はいつも私の後ろをくっついて歩いていて
That child was always walking right behind me...
いつの間にか一人で自分の夢に向かって突き進んでいて えっと…
Before I knew it, pressing forward alone toward her own dream... um...
みんなも応援してあげてください!
Everyone, please cheer for her too!
My little angel, I love you せーの!
My little angel, I love you, ready, set!
I love you
My little angel, I love you せーの!
My little angel, I love you, ready, set!
I love you
陰口なんて気にしている場合じゃないでしょ
This isn't the time to care about gossip, right?
平等にチャンスはあるから 負けるな私!
It's do or die, isn't it... don't lose, me!
あなたの描く夢 私の描く夢 叶えよう約束ね
The dream you draw, the dream I draw, let's make it come true, it's a promise
小指を重ねよう
Let's interlock our little fingers
あなたの夢は右で 私の夢は左
Your dream is on the right, my dream is on the left
ゆらゆらと迷っても どこかできっと繋がる
Even if we waver unsteadily, we'll surely connect somewhere
泣きたい時は泣いて 笑いたい時は笑って
When you want to cry, cry, when you want to laugh, laugh
疲れたら休みましょう 困ったら相談乗るから
When you get tired, let's take a rest, if you're troubled, I'll listen
理由があるとするれば あなたは私の天使
If there's a reason, you are my angel
my little sister, I love you
my little angel, very very cute
Do you know what I mean?
目指せよ快眠
Let's aim for a good sleep!
勝ち取れ安眠
Win us some good sleep!
いざ夢の世界へ
Running to the perfect world of dreams!
理想の眠りを求めて
I will keep on searching for the sleep that I love
さあ始めようおやすみ
Let's start right now and say goodnight!
私は囚われの姫
I'm a princess in a castle far away
魔王の城の中で 一人閉じ込められては
Trapped by the devil in his castle, I wait to be saved
毎日ひたすらに眠ってます
All I want is to keep on sleeping soundly every day!
今宵も布団に入り
I'll spend tonight in a casket so sweet
栖夜スヤリスト生活
Living my life so comfy and so cozy
枕もシーツも硬くて眠れない
But the pillows, and all the sheets are so hard and scratchy, I can't sleep!
(君を寝具にしてやろうか!)
(I'm gonna make you into my perfect bedding!)
目指せよ快眠
Let's aim for a good sleep!
勝ち取れ安眠
Win us some good sleep!
いざ夢の世界へ
Running to the perfect world of dreams!
ふかふかの枕を手に入れて
Gonna make myself a super fluffy pillow now
この疲れ癒したい
Then I can finally get some sleep!
恐れず前進 ほぐせよ全身
Move past any nightmares, you can face your worst fears
瞼を閉じたなら
If you gently close your tired eyes
すべすべのシーツの上で
On the smoothest silky sheets, I know I'll find rest
さあ始めようおやすみ
Let's start right now and say goodnight!
私は囚われの姫
I'm a princess in a castle far away
悲鳴が響く夜に 一人で牢を抜け出し
Where screams echo through the night, sneaking out of my cell all alone
今日も お散歩へと行ってきます
I'll go for a walk again today
数多の試練を超えて 新たな寝具の元へ
Pushing past countless trials toward new bedding
目指せよ快眠
Aim for a good sleep,
勝ち取れ安眠
win peace of mind,
いざ夢の世界へ
now to the world of dreams.
理想の眠りを求めて
Seeking the ideal sleep,
さあ始めようおやすみ
now let's start, good night.
つかめよ快眠
Grasp good sleep,
つかれて安眠
win peaceful sleep,
いざ夢のむこうへ
now to the other side of dreams.
ハイテン目覚まし手に入れて
Get an alarm clock to wake up,
気持ちよく目覚めたい
I want to wake up feeling great.
まだまだ前進
Still moving forward,
華麗に変身
brilliantly transforming.
ごはんを食べたなら
Once you've eaten meals,
魔法のベッドにダイブして
dive into the magic bed.
さあ始めようおやすみ
Now let's start, good night.
明日はもっと今日よりずっと
Tomorrow will be even more so than today,
いい夢見れるかな
I wonder if I can dream a good dream.
ふわふわの羽に包まれて
Wrapped in fluffy feathers,
こころゆくまで眠りたい
I want to sleep until my heart's content.
目指せよ快眠 勝ち取れ安眠
Aim for a good sleep, win peace of mind,
いざ夢の世界へ
now to the world of dreams.
理想の眠りを求めて
Seeking the ideal sleep,
さあ始めようおやすみ
now let's start, good night.
もうあと五分おやすみ
Just five more minutes, good night.
ノンレム睡眠 レム睡眠
Non-REM sleep, REM sleep,
すやぁ~
Suyaa~
う～む このマスコット可愛いな...
Hmm... This mascot is so cute...
へぇ、野球か...もしかしたら球場にいるかもだよ！行ってみる？
Eh, baseball...? Maybe they're at the stadium! Want to go check it out?
えっ！？行ってみたい！行ってみたい！
Eh?! I want to go! I want to go!
チケットとってみるよ！何日空いてる？
I'll get tickets! What days are you free?
み、ミオちゃん...きゅんっ！
M... Mio-chan... <3!
うわああ！ミオちゃん、ここを押さえたら勝ちってこと...！？
Waaah! Mio-chan, pressing here means we win...?!
そうだよそうだよ！こんな激アツな試合が見れるなんて...！
That's right, that's right! To be able to see such a thrilling game...!
ってこれって...
Th-Then this is...
ホームランだよ！おかゆホームランだよ！
A home run! Okayu, it's a home run!
す、すごい！野球すっげーーーっ！！
S-So amazing! Baseball is awesomeーー!!
どこまでも続くような青の季節は
The blue season that seems to continue forever,
四つ並ぶ眼の前を遮るものは何もない
there is nothing blocking the four eyes lined up in front.
アスファルト、蝉時雨を反射して
Reflecting the asphalt, the cicada's drizzle,
きみという沈黙が聞こえなくなる
the silence called you can no longer be heard.
この日々が色褪せる 僕と違うきみの匂いを知ってしまっても
These days are fading, even if I know your scent that is different from mine.
置き忘れてきた永遠の底に
In the depths of eternity left behind,
今でも青が澱んでいる 今でも青が澄んでいる
blue still resides there, blue is still clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も 近づけるのに、届かなかった
No matter what prayers or words could get closer, they couldn't reach.
まるで、静かな恋のような
Like a quiet love,
頬を伝った夏のような色の中
like the summer color that ran down the cheeks.
きみを呪う言葉がずっとのどの奥につかえてる
The words cursing you are still stuck in the back of my throat.
また会えるよねって 声にならない声
"We'll meet again," a voice that couldn't be heard.
昼下がり じめつく風の季節は
The muggy wind of the mid-afternoon season,
思い返す まだ何者でもなかった僕らの肖像
thinking back, the portraits of us who were still nothing.
何もかも 分かち合えたはずだった
We should have been able to share everything.
あの日から 少しずつ きみと違う僕という呪いがとっていく
Little by little since that day, the curse of me being different from you is taking hold.
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
見落とした孤独闇少しで
...I lost sight of.
徒花と咲いて散っていく君にさよなら
Farewell to you, who bloom like withered flowers...
今でも青が澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is deepening.
今でも青は澄んでいる
Even now, the blue is clear.
どんな祈りも言葉も近づけるのに届かなかった
No prayer or words could ever reach you.
まるで静かな恋のような 頬を伝った夏の様な色の中
Like a quiet voice or a fleeting summer heat...
君を祝う言葉がずっと喉の奥に繋がってる
The words praising you echo deep within me.
「また会えるよって」
"We'll meet again," you said.
声にならない声
A voice that could no longer be a voice.
無限に膨張する銀河の星の粒のような指の隙間をこぼれた
Like stardust scattered through the infinite night sky, leaving cracks in time.
すっかり野球1人でも見に来るようになってしまったな…
Somehow, I've ended up coming to watch baseball games all by myself...
ご飯並んでるうちにスターティングメンバー発表されたぞ…
While waiting for my meal, the starting lineup was announced.
…ってえ？
Wait, what?
スターマン？
Starman?
(手招きする動作)
*(Gesturing to follow)*
え？えぇ？
Eh? Ehh?!
スターマンがこっそり僕についてこいって言ってる…
Starman is secretly telling me to follow him...
どういうことーーーーー！？！？！？！
What does that even mean?!?!?
ライトからレフトまで横浜ジャンジャン盛り上がって行こうジャン！
From right to left, Yokohama, let's get hyped up!
好きです！！Baseball！打って行こう！
I love Baseball! Let's go hit!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball!
ヨコジャンハマジャン燃え萌えジャン！目指すのはあの星ジャンジャンJUMP！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, burning bright-jan! Aim for that star, jump, jump, jump!
ヨコジャンハマジャンイケイケジャン！ドキドキウキウキBaseball！
Yoko-jan, Hama-jan, let's go-jan! Thrilling and exciting Baseball!
ニッポンの元気だ横浜ジャン！みんなの夢のせジャンジャンジャン！
Nippon's energy is Yokohama-jan! Catching everyone's dreams, jump, jump, jump!
スーパープレーで燃え萌えジャン！汗も涙も星になれ☆
Super play, burning bright! Sweat and tears will become a star!
さあみんな両手合わせてハッピー・スター☆ダンス まだまだ足りないよー！ほらほら！
Come on everyone, put your hands together for Happy Star Dance! There's still not enough! Come on, come on!
アイラブ横浜！OK〜！まだまだ打って行こう！！
I love Yokohama! OK~! Let's keep hitting!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
ガッチリガッチリガッチリガッチリ守ってキャッチ！ガッチリガッチリ愛してはなさない💙
Catch it tightly, tightly, love it and never let go!
打って打って打って打って打ってカッと飛ばして！宇宙に飛んでけ星になれ☆
Hit, hit, hit, hit, hit, smash it, and fly away into space, become a star!
好きです！！Baseball！好きです！！Baseball！
I love Baseball! I love Baseball!
いちたすにたすスターマン♪ しかくさんかくスターマン♪
One plus two plus Starman, square, triangle Starman!
星型フェイスのスターマン♪ 星型肉球スターマン♪
Star-shaped face Starman, star-shaped paws Starman!
かけきくけここキララちゃん♪ ハッピーラッキーキララちゃん♪
Dash, dash, dash, dash, Kirara-chan! Happy, lucky, Kirara-chan!
リズムに合わせてキララちゃん♪ キラキラおどるよキララちゃん♪
Dance to the rhythm, Kirara-chan, dancing sparkly, Kirara-chan!
さあみんなで声あわせ 横浜の星 DeNA ベイスターズ
Come on everyone, let's raise our voices together for Yokohama's star, DeNA Baystars!
DeNA ベイスターズ DeNA ベイスターズ
DeNA Baystars, DeNA Baystars!
すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan!
みんなの夢をあつめる すっすっすたすたスターマン♪
Gathering everyone's dreams, su, su, su, sutasuta Starman!
きききらきらキララちゃん♪ みんなの笑顔をつくるよ
Ki, ki, kirakira Kirara-chan, creating everyone's smiles!
レッツゴー！
Let's go!
はい！ということで
Yes! So,
横浜DeNAベイスターズのスターマンが特別ゲストで来てくれましたー！
Yokohama DeNA BayStars' Starman has come as a special guest!
かわいい！本物のだよ！可愛すぎるぅ！
So cute! The real deal! Too cute!
おかゆ 誕生日おめでとうだって！
"Happy Birthday, Okayu!"
うわー、ありがとうスターマン！
Wow, thank you, Starman!
え待って、暑い。あの、これ出しきっちゃったけど、
Wait, it's hot. Um, I've already shown this,
一旦これだけ言わせて。ベイスターズ日本一 本当におめでとうー！
but let me say just this first. Congratulations on winning the Japan Series, BayStars!
あ、すごい喜んでいる！
Ah, he's so happy!
かわいい！いや、私ね、スターマンに一目惚れして...
So cute! You know, I fell in love with Starman at first sight...
野球もね、好きになったんだよ。あー、もう胸いっぱいです。
and came to like baseball too. Ah, my heart is full.
さ、可愛い喜んでくれてる。
He's so happily cute.
えでもね、スターマンに謝らなきゃいけないことがあって...
But you know, there's something I have to apologize to Starman for...
その、僕、最初スターマンのこと猫だと思ってて、もう僕のね、仲間なのかなって思ったんだけど...
that, you know, at first I thought Starman was a cat, and thought, "Ah, is he a comrade of mine?" but...
あ、やばい。怒ってる怒ってる。ファンの人にタヌキって言われて、ぼこってされた時にヤッホー投げだ！すごい、身のこなしやばいな、生で見ると。
Ah, oh no. He's mad, he's mad. When fans called him a raccoon dog and got beaten up, that Yahoo throw! Amazing, his agility is incredible seeing it live.
え、え、スターマン、スターマン。あの、ちょっとね、お願りなんだけど...よかったら一緒に写真撮ってもらえないかなー！あー！嬉しいー！
Um, Starman, Starman. I have a little request... Would you take a picture with me if you don't mind? Ah! I'm so happy!
え、じゃあ写真一緒に撮りたい。どうしよう、ポーズは。ねこのポーズ一緒に撮ってくれたりする？
Then I want to take a picture together. What should we do for a pose? Would you do a cat pose with me?
あ！ありがとう！じゃあ、ちょっとここら辺で、スターマンもこっちちょっと来て。女性なのでねこのポーズするよ。せーの、
Ah! Thank you! Well then, around here, Starman come over here a bit. Since we're both ladies, we'll do the cat pose. Ready,
にゃーん！え、可愛い！可愛いけどさ、せっかくだからちょっとカメラさん、カメラマンさ、こっちでもっと...
Meow! So cute! But since we have the chance, cameraman, over here more...
あ、そうそうそう、可愛い！可愛すぎる！にゃーん！スターマン、なんでこんなに可愛いんだろう。ありがとうスターマン！
Ah, yes, yes, so cute! Too cute! Meow! Starman, why are you so cute? Thank you, Starman!
はあ、もう幸せすぎるな。もう何の後悔もございません、私の人生には。
Haah, I'm too happy. I have no regrets left in my life.
なんか持ってるスターマン。何それ？ええ！それ！スターマンのサインじゃないの！？え、いいの貰っちゃって！
Starman's holding something. What is that? Eh?! That! Isn't that Starman's autograph?! Eh, can I really have it?!
え！ありがとうスターマンいいのかな、いいのかな。あ、ありがとう。え、あ、じょ、じょ、じょ、じょ、じょー！
Eh? Thank you Starman, is it okay? Ah, thank you. Eh, ah, jo, jo, jo, jo, joor!
やばいよこれ。最高すぎる。
This is crazy. It's too amazing.
はあ、何回見てもサインが。ありがとうスターマン。大事にしとくからね！はい、じゃ、はい、しょっと。
Haah, no matter how many times I look at this autograph. Thank you Starman. I'll treasure it! Yes, well, hold on.
はあ、もうこれだけでも十分幸せなんだけど、もしよかったら、もう1曲一緒に踊ってくれませんか？
Haah, just this is already plenty of happy, but if you'd like, would you dance one more song with me?
あー！オッケーいただきました！え、何歌う？何歌う？スターマン。悩んでいる。
Ah! Got an OK! Eh, what should we sing? What should we sing, Starman? He's pondering.
もぐもぐしてるね。可愛い！ということは、あの曲だね！それじゃあ一緒に歌おう！もぐもぐYUMMY！
He's chomping away. Cute! That means it's that song! Well then, let's sing together! Mogu Mogu YUMMY!
森羅万象の悪戦苦闘も
Even the struggles against all creation
マヨネーズかけたら大体おいしくなる?
become pretty delicious if you add mayonnaise?
君が泣いてもお腹は空くよ
Even if you cry, your stomach still gets empty
消化できなかった ごめん ごめん。
I couldn't digest it, sorry, sorry.
スイも甘いも勝手に食べて
Eating whatever sweets and sours I want,
ご迷惑おかけしています
I'm causing you trouble.
パクチーな丘 変な味のジュース
A hill of cilantro, a strangely flavored juice,
心を無にして飲み込みます ah!
I swallow it with a blank mind, ah!
混沌情報過多の レストラン で
In a chaotic, information-overloaded restaurant,
嘘っぱちの メニュー に お茶 こぼして
Spilling tea on the bogus menu,
君と もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Chomp, chomp, munching away with you
銃撃戦の 真ん中 で もぐもぐ
Chomp, chomp, right in the middle of a gunfight
魑魅魍魎 ハラペコ の 群れ
A hungry pack of monsters and phantoms
満腹になる未来を願っているよ もぐもぐ
Hoping for a future where we're full, mogu-mogu
もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Mogu-mogu, mogu-mogu
世界が終わる前に
Before the world ends
もぐもぐやみぃ まちかみぃ
Mogu-mogu Yummy! Magic Coming!
よむよむありのまんま
Reading and reading, just as it is
もぐもぐやみぃ まちかみぃ
Mogu-mogu Yummy! Magic Coming!
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Savoring this world, uma-uma
理論武装のミルフィーユサンド
A mille-feuille sandwich of theoretical armor
匿名希望のオーロラソース
Aurora sauce from an anonymous sender
大雑把な味付けお目にみてよ
Overlook the rough seasoning, won't you?
おいしくなったらオッケーオッケー
If it tastes good, then it's okay, okay
いいも悪いもいっぱい食べて
Eat plenty of both good and bad
汚れた口元拭います
Wiping my stained mouth clean now
おにぎり ピザ ケーキ 豪華なフルコース
Rice balls, pizza, cake, a luxurious full course
罠を歌うたび気を付けます
Every time I sing of traps, I'll be careful
猛獣激昂のバイキングで
In this fierce beast-rage of a buffet
独り占めと絶品料理より分けて
Separating hogged items from exquisite dishes
君ともぐもぐ もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Mogu-mogu with you, mogu-mogu, mogu-mogu
デスゲームの教室でもぐもぐ
Mogu-mogu even in a death game classroom
寿命も両立払ってこの群れ
Balancing our lifespans, paying for this flock
仲の良い君と生き延びられたら
If we can survive together with you, my close friend
いいのもぐもぐ もぐもぐ
That's good, mogu-mogu, mogu-mogu
数年後もこの場所で もぐもぐ もぐもぐ
Mogu-mogu, mogu-mogu in this place years from now
もぐもぐやみぃ まちかみぃ
Mogu-mogu Yummy! Magic Coming!
今夜の晩御飯は
Tonight's dinner is
もぐもぐやみぃ まちかみぃ
Mogu-mogu Yummy! Magic Coming!
次はお前の番だ
Next is your turn
もぐもぐやみぃ まちかみぃ
Mogu-mogu Yummy! Magic Coming!
よむよむありのまんま
Reading and reading, just as it is
もぐもぐやみぃ まちかみぃ
Mogu-mogu Yummy! Magic Coming!
この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Savoring this world, uma-uma
もぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐ もぐもぐやみぃ
Mogu-mogu-mogu-mogu-mogu-mogu, mogu-mogu Yummy!
もぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐ もぐもぐやみぃ やみぃ さま でした
Mogu-mogu-mogu-mogu-mogu-mogu, mogu-mogu Yummy! Thank you for the meal!
はー
Ah...
みんなもゲストとして参加してくれてすごい嬉しかったしさ、
I was so happy that everyone participated as guests too,
スターマンがまさか国の誕生日をお祝いしに来てくれるなんて、
I never expected Starman to come all the way to celebrate my country's birthday,
もう僕は満足でしにそうだよ。
I'm practically going to die from happiness.
あ、そうでした。
Oh, that's right.
とりあえずここでまず一つ目の告知です。どうぞ。
First of all, here is our first announcement. Go ahead.
2ndアルバム発売決定！！
[2nd Album Release Confirmed!]
ペルソニャリスペクト
[Perosonya Respect]
2025.5.14 2ndアルバム
[Release Date: May 14, 2025]
楽曲提供アーティスト
[Featured Artists Announcement]
配信終了後より予約開始！！
[Pre-orders start after the stream!]
あ、テザームービーも終わってた。
Ah, the teaser movie is already over.
はい、僕のセカンドフルアルバム「ペルソニャリスペクト」の発売が決定しました！やったー！
Yes! The release of my second full album, "Perosonya Respect," has been decided! Yay!
2024年2月にリリースした「ネコカブリーナ」に加えて、8曲の新曲をこのアルバムのために制作した全9曲入りです。
In addition to "Neko Kaburina" released in February 2024, it features 9 tracks including 8 new songs.
9曲の9曲！
Nine songs of nine songs!
デコニナさん、FLG4さん、koyoriさん、R Sound Designさん、TOOBOEさん、稲葉曇さん、式浦躁吾さん、神山羊さん、
Deco*27-san, FLG4-san, koyori-san, R Sound Design-san, TOOBOE-san, Inaba Cumori-san, Shikiura Sogo-san, Kamiyama Yoyo-san,
今回新曲の制作にはとっても豪華な作家さんに参加していただきました。ありがとうございます！
Extremely luxurious creators participated in producing the new songs this time. Thank you very much!
今日はアルバムから先行シングルを1曲披露したいと思います。
Today, I'd like to perform one pre-release single from the album.
それでは聞いてください。いくぞー！
Now then, please listen. Here we go!
キスだけでいいからね 一日だけね
Just a kiss is fine, just for one day
それだけでもいいから 私を
Even if it's just that, hold me...
あなたは まだ 私の
You still don't know
こころを知らない
my heart,
溜め息混じりでも
Even with a sigh mixed in,
その気になっちゃう
getting carried away,
それがいや
I hate that.
見え透いた優しさで
With transparent kindness,
気が向いたら思い出して
if you feel like it, remember me,
残されるくらいなら
If I'm going to be left behind,
騙されるほうがいいわ
I'd rather be deceived.
キスだけでいいからね
Just a kiss is fine,
それだけで私はいいの
that's all I need.
交差する いつまでもこのままで
Crossing, staying this way forever,
繋いでる時間だけ
only for the time we're connected
居なくなっていいからね
it's fine if you disappear...
私は まだ あなたの
I still want to hear
言葉が聞きたい
your words,
何気ないことでも
Even casual things
また気になっちゃう だからいや
make me care again, so I hate that.
行き過ぎた優しさで
With excessive kindness,
気が付いたら虚しくなる
before I know it, I feel empty.
嘘をついて傷だらけ
Lying and covered in scars,
そんなことどうでもいいわ
I don't care about things like that.
キスだけでいいからね それだけで私はいいの
Just a kiss is fine, that's all I need.
交差する いつまでもこのままで
Crossing, staying this way forever,
繋いでる時間だけ
only for the time we're connected
二人になって
Becoming two,
キスだけでいいからね
just a kiss is fine.
今だけでいいからね
Just for now is fine,
本当は痛くなってしまうけど
though it actually starts to hurt,
このままでいいからね
It's still fine to stay this way,
いいからね
it's fine.
キスだけでいいからね
Just a kiss is fine...
いやー
Whew—
コントローラー動いたんですけど
My controller moved, though!
はい ということで
Yes, so,
セカンドアルバムから新曲「キスだけでいいからね」でしたー！
that was the new song "Just a kiss is fine" from my second album!
大人っぽかったかな？
Was it mature?
この曲は 神山羊さんに制作していただきました！
This song was produced by Yoh Kamiyama!
前回かき下ろしていただいた「コハク」とはね、また違った雰囲気のサウンドで、
With a different musical atmosphere from "Kohaku" which you wrote for me last time,
もう素敵だなと思いました。
I thought it was just wonderful.
僕もね、このお披露目するときに、こんな綺麗な歌僕に歌いこなせるのかなみたいな気持ちがあったんですけど、
When I was revealing this, I felt like, "Can I really pull off such a pretty song?"
みんな喜んでくれたよね？
But everyone was happy about it, right?
このあと配信終了後にMVの公開、24時から先行配信もあるので、楽しみにしてて下さいね！
After the stream ends, the MV will premiere, and early streaming starts at midnight, so please look forward to it!
さらにこちらの「キスだけでいいからね」が、オリジナルゲーム「おかゆにゅーむ！」のエンディングテーマになります！
Furthermore, "Just a kiss is fine" will be the ending theme for the game "Okayu Nyuum!"!
クリアしないと危ないよ！
You'll be in trouble if you don't clear it!
ついに来週27日木曜日に発売です！ あっという間だったなー。
It's finally releasing next week on Thursday, the 27th! It went by so fast.
いやーついにね、発売しちゃいますということで、なんか自分のことなのに自分のことじゃないような。
Well, since it's finally releasing, it feels like it's about me, yet not about me.
ずっとそんな気持ちだったんですが、まあ発売楽しみです！
I've felt that way the whole time, but well, I'm looking forward to the release!
予約できてないよって人は、
If you haven't reserved yours yet,
各販売店さんと
be sure to check out participating stores!
ダウンロード版もあるのでチェックしてみてね！
There's also a digital download version, so check that out!
合わせてアニメイトさんで発売記念抽選会が実施予定なので、
Plus, a lottery for the release celebration event with Animate will be held,
詳細は公式ホームページとエンタグラムさんの公式Xを要チェックです！
so check the official website and X (Twitter) for details!
この曲だけでいいからねにが収録されるアルバムなのですが、
While this album only includes previously released songs,
今回初めてホロライブプロダクション公式ショップ限定販売の数量限定版もリリースしまーす！
this time, we're releasing a limited-quantity physical version for the first time via the hololive production official shop!
こちらの2枚のアルバムキービジュアルが飾って楽しめるスペシャルボックス仕様となっておりまーす！
This limited edition features a special box where the two album key visuals can be displayed by sliding and flipping the cover.
ボックスの中にはアルバムデザインのアクリルスタンドはトールサイズケース、さらにホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームのおかゆカードも収録されておりますー！
It also includes an album-designed acrylic stand, a tall-size case, and a hololive Official Card Game PR card featuring an Okayu card!
こなきなこ先生、石原たつや先生描き下ろしのイラストを両方飾って楽しめる、
Both illustrations by Konakina-ko Sensei and Ishihara Tatsuya Sensei are featured, so you can enjoy both!
数量限定版の購入は先着順となっておりますので、
Since the limited edition is available on a first-come, first-served basis,
お見逃しなく！おにぎり先着順とかも慣れなさそうで心配なんですけど大丈夫おにぎり。
don't miss out! Getting onigiri on a first-come basis isn't something you're used to, but you'll be fine, onigiri!
続きまして、全国のCDショップで買える通常版には店舗別特典が付きますー！お店ごとにたくさん種類があるのでぜひチェックしてみてください！
Additionally, purchasing the standard edition at CD shops nationwide comes with store-specific bonuses, so be sure to check them out as there are plenty of options!
セカンドアルバム『ぺるそにゃりすぺくと』の発売までいろんな情報解禁があると思いますので、それぞれ楽しみにしていてねー！えへへ。
Stay tuned for more updates leading up to the release of her 2nd album, "Personya Respect"!
え？え？なに？まだあるの？
Eh? What? There's more?
2nd Live 開催決定
2nd Live Confirmed!
coming soon
セカンドライブ決定ーー！
Her 2nd Live has been decided!
うわー！なんか会場大きかったよね！
Waaah! The venue was so big!
待って、もうパンピ出てゆ。
Wait, did it already reveal?
チケットとかライブについての詳細は後日発表するので、楽しみにしててね！
Ticket details and live specifics will be announced at a later date, so please look forward to them!
ちなみにアルバムとライブ共通のハッシュタグはこちらです！ぜひたくさん呟いてくださいねだって！
By the way, the hashtag for both the album and live is right here, so please tweet a lot!
え？ま、なんかもう、街？ほら、みんな僕のライブ来てくれる、来てくれるのかな？
Eh? Wait, is the venue really going to have people? Will everyone come to my live?
不安だよ、不安だよ。でも楽しみだよ。
I'm nervous, I'm nervous, but I'm excited too!
情緒行かれちまった。
I'm getting all emotional, haha.
ええと、次が最後の告知です！どどーん！
And now, for the final announcement... Tada!
猫又おかゆ誕生日記念グッズが出まーす！
Nekomata Okayu Birthday Festival 2025 commemorative goods are out!
それじゃ、1つずつ商品見ていきましょう！まずは、こちら！
Let's go through the items one by one. First is this!
どどーん！ごろごろラバーマット！
Tada! The "Gorogoro Rubber Mat"!
イラストは僕のママ神岡ちろる先生に描き下ろしていただきましたー！
It features an illustration drawn just for me by Kamioka Chiruru Sensei!
ラバーマットはね、結構前にグッズで出したことあったんだけど、まあそろそろね、まあ使い続けてる人のラバーマットももしかしたらそろそろ替え時かなってなってたり、
I've released rubber mats as merch before, but lately, I've been thinking that people using them might be thinking it's about time for a new one,
それこそ当時はおかゆのこと知らなかったっていう人がさ、買ってなかったりする時期になってきたのかなと思って、
or maybe some people didn't even know me back then, so I decided to release a new one!
ラバーマット出してみました！かわいいでしょ？僕めちゃごろごろしてんの。
It's super cute, right? I use mine all the time and roll around on it!
めちゃめちゃみんなやってって聞きますし、そういうのに使ったりとか、パソコンの前に置いて使うのもとてもいいと思いますー！
And I think it'd be super nice to put it in front of a PC or something and use it!
へへへへー！
Hehehe!
続きまして、こちらー！
Moving right along, here is this!
ライブ映えもばっちりおおかゆTシャツー！
The super live-ready Okayu T-shirt!
Tシャツもね、すごい前に出したことあったけど、ライブに来てくんだったらこのTシャツマジで神じゃない...
This T-shirt is seriously God-tier if you're coming to the live, so...
とゆことで、
with that in mind,
選ばせていただきました！描きおろしはシズさんですー！
I got to design it! The illustration is by Shizu-san!
シズ先生ありがとうございますー！
Shizu-sensei, thank you so much!
めっちゃかっこいいでしょー？
Super cool, right?
まあ、こんなかっこいい猫又おかゆを見れるのはこのTシャツだけかもしれない、
This cool Nekomata Okayu might be the only way to see one like this!
ということで、ぜひみなさんこれを着てね、ライブとかいろんなところ遊びに行ってくださーい！普段使いもしやすいよねー？
So definitely wear this to the live or when you're going out and about! It's super easy to wear day-to-day, too!
へへへへー！
Hehehe!
はい！続いては、こちらー！
Alright, next up is this!
気づいた？実は、おかゆのズボンモチーフリュック！ふふふっ(笑)
Did you notice? It's actually the Okayu shorts-motif backpack! Hahaha!
いや、これは僕のね、通常衣装のズボンをモチーフにしたデザインのリュックとなっておりますー！
Yeah, this is a design made into a backpack featuring my usual outfit's shorts!
フロントポケットには、ホロふれがね、2こ、2体、2匹、はいる設計となっておりますー！
The front pocket is designed to fit two holofle- Oh wait, two? Two of what? Two creatures? No, two-
チャームもさ、カチッ！猫でかわいいでしょ？へへへー！
The charm is also a cute cat, right? Hehe!
これはマジでね、カバーさんにお願いして最後までこだわりましたー！
This is seriously something I asked Cover about and fussed over down to the very last detail!
横についてるタグみたいなやつは、僕のね、通常衣装の靴をね、衣装、衣装じゃなくて、あれなんですよ、イメージしたものになっているんですねー！
The tag-like thing on the side isn't my usual outfit's shoes, but rather... based on my image of them!
まあ、去年の生誕ライブでは僕のここに、おにぎりが描いてあるパーカーを出したから、まあそれとセットでね、こうやってリュックを背負ったら、まあなんか遠めに見ると横になってるおかゆみたいに見えるんじゃないかなって思ってますー！
Well, last year's birthday live had a parka with onigiri drawn on it, so I thought if you wear the backpack together with that, from afar it might look kinda like Okayu!
最近はね、ぬいぐるみをつれてライブに来てくれてる人が多いので、ぬいぐるみを目入れられるデザインにしてみましたー！
Lately, lots of people bring plushies to the live, so I made a design where you can fit a plushie inside!
へへへへー！
Hehehe!
はい！続いては、こちらー！
Alright, next is this!
保存しやすいチェキホルダーとなっておりますー！
An easy-to-store cheki holder!
イラストはね、あの僕がデザインさせていただきましたー！
The illustration is, well... one I got to design myself!
こちらは、ま、よく出したりするチェキが入れられるサイズとなっておりますー！
This is sized so you can put chekis you collect in it!
ま、それこそねさっき発表があったリュックにつけていくもよしだしー！
And of course, attaching it to the backpack we just announced is also a great option!
ま、飾るために、チェキを入れるためのチェキホルダーとしてお部屋に飾ったりなんかしても絶対かわいいよねー？映えを意識してオーロラ加工していただいておりますー！
To show off your chekis, we've treated it with an aurora finish to make them pop!
ふうー！息ちょっと整えて。
Phew, let's catch my breath.
はい！続いては、こちらー！
Alright, next is this!
フルセット購入特典ー！
Full set purchase bonus!
今回もございます！フルセット特典、直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと特典ボイスがついてきまーす！いぇーい！いぇーい！どんどんぱふぱふー！
We've got the full set bonus again this time: a foil-stamped autographed cheki-style bromide card and a special voice! Yay, yay, puff-puff!
今回もね、無制限でやらせていただきましたから、みんな急がなくて大丈夫です！ゆっくり買ってくれれば大丈夫なんです。
Now, this time too, we're making it uncapped, so don't rush, buy it at your own pace, it's totally fine!
はい！特製ボイスタイトルは、
Alright, the special voice title is...
「おかゆぬいぐるみとおでかけ編　ぬいぐるみ視点の珍しいチュチュエーション」となっておりますー！
"Okayu Plushie & Outing Edition: A Rare Situation Where You're Inside the Backpack Plushie."
ま、さっきのリュックにね、あのふたつ入りあっ...て言ったんで、そのぬいぐるみがリュックの中にいるときは、どういう景色を楽しんでてどういう気持ちなのかなっていうのをイメージしたボイスとなっておりますー！
It's a voice imagining what kind of scenery and feelings the plushie experiences when it's inside the backpack we talked about earlier.
ぜひ、おかゆのリュックに入れて聞くと臨場感があって楽しめるボイスとなっておりまーす！
Put the Okayu plushie in your backpack and listen to it for an immersive, heartwarming voice experience!
続いては、こちらー！
Next is this!
プロモカードー！
Promo card!
タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、去年の9月から発売されたホロライブ公式カードゲームで使用できるカードが1枚ついてきまーす！
As a full set bonus for the talent and premium merch, you'll get one card you can use in the Hololive Official Card Game released since last September!
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップでご購入された
These cards can be purchased at the Hololive Production Official Shop.
“Oh my god”
"Oh my god"
愛のネタバレ 「別れ」っぽだな
That's a spoiler for love, feeling like a "breakup"
人生のネタバレ 「死ぬ」っぽだな
That's a spoiler for life, feeling like "death"
なにそれ意味深でかっこいいじゃん…
So full of deep meaning, isn't it cool...
それっぽい単語集で踊ってんだ
Dancing away to a collection of buzzwords like that
失敬
Pardon me
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu style
っぽいじゃん っぽいじゃん
Ain't it? Ain't it?
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu style
神っぽいな
That's god-ish.
もういいぜ もういいぜ それ
That's enough, that's enough
もういいぜ もういいぜ 逆に興奮してきたなァ
That's enough, that's enough, I'm getting excited on the contrary
おっけいね おっけいね 夢 おっけいね おっけいね
It's big, it's big, your dream, it's big, it's big
景気いいけど 品性はTHE END
Profitable, yet graciousness is the end
うぇええい うぇええい “Gott ist tot”
Wry, wry "Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
That's god-ish, how unfair
神っぽいな それ “My God”
That's god-ish, that's "My God"
アイウォンチー ウォンチー IQが下がっていく感じ
I want you, want you, feeling my IQ going down
邪心っぽいな それ 畢竟
That's devil-ish, after all
邪心っぽいな それ “My God”
That's devil-ish, that's "My God"
アイヘイチー ヘイチー 害虫はどっち
I hate you, hate you, which one is the pest?
その髪型 その目 その口元
That hairstyle, those eyes, that mouth
その香水 その服 そのメイク
That perfume, that outfit, that makeup
アレルっぽいな それ 比況
That's like— how unfair
アレルっぽいな それ その名言 その意見 その批評
That's like— those quotes, those opinions, those reviews
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That charisma, those gags, that sense
神っぽいな それ 卑俗 っぽい っぽい っぽい 憧れちゃう！
That's god-ish, how unfair, -ish, -ish, -ish, I admire it!
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu style
っぽいじゃん っぽいじゃん
Ain't it? Ain't it?
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu style
神っぽいな
That's god-ish.
メタ思考する本質は悪意？
Is the essence of meta-thinking malice?
人を小馬鹿にしたような作為
Artifice that mocks people as fools
無為に生き延びるのは難しい
It's hard to survive by doing nothing
権力に呑まれて揺らぐ灯り
A flickering light swallowed by power
神を否定し神に成り代わり
Denying God and replacing Him
玉座で豹変する小物達
Small fries transforming on the throne
批判に見せかけ自戒の祈り Do you know?
Disguising criticism as a prayer of self-reflection, Do you know?
何言ってんの？ それ ウザい
What are you talking about? That's annoying
何言ってんの？ それ 意味がよくわかんないし
What are you talking about? I don't really understand the meaning
寝付いちゃうよ マジ 飽きっぽいんだよ
I'll fall asleep, seriously, I get bored easily
オーケー 飽きっぽいんだよ オーケー
Okay, I get bored easily, okay
踊れるやつ ちっちゃいね 器
Those who can dance are so small-minded
天才ゆえ孤独ですね “Gott ist tot”
You're lonely because you're a genius, "Gott ist tot"
神っぽいな それ 卑俗
That's god-ish, how unfair
神っぽいな それ “My God”
That's god-ish, that's "My God"
超健康 健康 言い張って くたばっていく感じ
Insisting you're super healthy, feeling like you're gonna croak
ヤケっぽいな それ 畢竟
That's desperate, after all
ヤケっぽいな それ “My God”
That's desperate, that's "My God"
もう哀愁 哀愁 そのタイトル その絵
Such pathos, pathos
その音楽 その歌 アレルっぽいな それ 比況
That title, that art, that music, that song
アレルっぽいな それ その名言 その意見 その批評
That's like— how unfair
そのカリスマ そのギャグ そのセンス
That charisma, those gags, that sense
神っぽいな それ 卑俗 っぽい っぽい っぽい 憧れちゃう！
That's god-ish, how unfair, -ish, -ish, -ish, I admire it!
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu style
っぽいじゃん っぽいじゃん
Ain't it? Ain't it?
とぅ とぅる とぅ とぅ とぅる “風”
Tu-turu-tu-tu-turu style
神っぽいな
That's god-ish.